onnanoko hajimemashita
A tired girl starts her day
tameiki wa bioron no shirabe ni nite
With a sigh like the moan of a violin
akai mi hajikechatta
A cherry bursts in her mouth
mada anata wo shiranai
This was before we had met
konna koto hajimetette
This is the first time I've ever felt like this
manazashi wa aku no hana sakimidarete mo
I could see that your pretty eyes were filled with contempt
ie e to tsuzuku
But I had to go home
basu sutoppu demo anata wa tsurenai
Even at the bus stop, you gave me the cold shoulder
karameta hanabi myaku utsu
The fireworks in the sky pulse
koi no shiruetto
In a silhouette of love
karui mahou
With a little magic,
usotsuki na kuchibiru
Two sets of lying lips
sou kasaneteru
Lock together
ano ne
You see
nee kamisama
God...
warui ko ni naritai yo
I'd like to be a naughty girl
ii ko ni shiteru kara
I'm tired of being good
onegai dayo
So, please
zurui koto sasetoite
It's for a good reason
ii koto shitai nara
So let me be bad for once
sukaato hirogaesu shite
By flipping my skirt
sugu kaeru yo
I'll be back soon
doyoubi wa haresou da
It looks like Saturday is going to be sunny
kamisama hajimemashita
God, it has already started
It's the guy sitting in the far back!
（女子生徒１）
いちばん後ろの席の人だよ
You're right! He's so cool!
（女子生徒２）
ホントかっこいい
Shriek
He stands out without doing anything. How am I supposed to deal with that?
（奈々生(ななみ)）
ちょっと目立ち過ぎて
どうしたものかという感じです
The God Asks A Boy Out On A Date
And I've been so busy lately
（奈々生）
にしても
最近いろいろ忙しかったから―
that I feel like I've barely been able to keep up with school.
今回は 範囲追いかけるのが
やっとって感じ
..Ujigami
High School
Ujigami High School is currently at the end of a term.
（講釈師）
宇治上(うじがみ)高校は ただいま学期末
When it comes to the end of a term, you have...
学期末といえば…
Stupid finals. They're almost as gross as these mushrooms.
（奈々生）
期末試験なんて―
しいたけの次に嫌い
Boo
Hoo
I told you not to put shiitake mushrooms in my lunches!
お弁当に しいたけ入れないでって
言ったのに―
Boo
Hoo
何で入れるのよ 巴衛(ともえ)
Boo
Hoo
Why do you still put them in?!
Boo
Hoo
What was that?
（巴衛）
わざとだ
Boo
Hoo
You are more than just a poor goddess.
（巴衛）
神としても未熟だが―
It seems you are an equally poor student as well.
ここでも 己の無能さに
苦労しているようだな 奈々生
If you do not have the brains to
keep up, you should just drop out.
頭が ついていかないようなら
学校など辞めてしまえ
Ignore
（女子生徒たち）
わあ～
Tomoe started coming to school to protect me, which made sense at the time, but now...
（奈々生）
巴衛が 私の護衛ということで
学校に通い始めたのはいいのですが
What is keeping you so busy?
何が忙しかったのだ
神の仕事もしてないくせに
You've barely done anything as the new land god.
Urk
I-It's a work in progress!
（奈々生）
それは そのうち…
He talks about work as a god,
but the things I can do aren't very...
神の仕事っていっても
私にできることなんか…
Yo, fox.
（鞍馬(くらま)）
よう きつね
（女子生徒たち）
キャーッ！
Tagging along with Nanami again?
今日も 奈々生のお供か？
精が出るな
Aren't you a hard worker?
And I see that you are still
shepherding a flock of naive sheep.
貴様こそ 女子の餌付けに
余念がないな
Sticking to her like a leech is a
surefire way to get her to hate you.
あんまり 金魚のふんみたく
くっついていると―
奈々生に嫌われんぜ
Yes, well...
さすが 既に嫌われているやつの
言うことは重みが違う
Coming from a guy she already hates, your words carry a certain weight.
She doesn't hate me.
嫌われてません～
You said something about devouring her heart, and now she hates you.
心臓食らうとか何とか言って
嫌われたではないか
I never said that to Nanami.
奈々生には言ってません～
They're both spirits, so I wish they'd just get along.
（奈々生）
せっかく 妖怪同士なんだから
仲良くすればいいのにな
What's wrong?
（奈々生）どうしたの
（あみ）えっ！
M-Momozono!
も… 桃園(ももぞの)さん！
ハァー
I still haven't been able to thank
Kurama for helping me the other day.
この前
鞍馬君に助けてもらったお礼―
まだ言えてなくて
But he's always surrounded by girls, so it's hard to approach him.
でも 鞍馬君
いつも女子に囲まれてるから―
話しかけづらくて
But I still think I need to thank him for what he's done.
でも 今日こそは
ちゃんと言わなきゃと思って
This is just...
（奈々生）
何か―
so frickin' adorable!
かわいいな こういうの
Okay, then. I'll get a hold of Kurama for you.
じゃあさ 私が
鞍馬を呼んできてあげるよ
What?
It'll be okay. I'll work something out so you can talk to him alone.
大丈夫　二人っきりで話せるように
何とかする
I've been meaning to ask you this for a long time now,
ずっと 聞こうと
思ってたんだけど―
but are you a medium or something?
桃園さんって
拝み屋さんか何かしてるの？
Medium?
拝み屋さん？
Because I mean, you did that ghost busting the other day.
だって この前
お化け退治してたでしょ？
Ghost busting?
お化け退治？
Oh, I haven't told anyone! I-I swear!
（あみ）
あっ 私 誰にも言ってないから
本当に！
Clue
less
We cannot blame dear Nanami for being clueless.
（講釈師）
奈々生ちゃん
キョトンも無理からぬ
Tomoe was the one who pulled that stunt the other
day when he went to school in sickly Nanami's stead.
先日 風邪ひき奈々生に代わって
登校した―
巴衛がやらかしたこと
Well...
そうだな
I don't think I'm anything special.
拝み屋さんっていうか―
But I guess you never know, right?
拝まれ屋さんかな
Huh?
（あみ）
ほえ？
I've found something I can do.
（奈々生）
私にできること 見つけた
Oh, my...
（鞍馬）
困ったな
I make it a rule not to accept gifts from my fans.
そういうの
もらわないことにしてるんだよね
Sorry about that.
ごめんね
He apologized to us!
（女子生徒１）
ごめんねって言われちゃった
Buying my albums is enough for me.
（鞍馬）
ＣＤ買ってくれればいいから…
（奈々生）
鞍馬
Kurama, hold still, please.
ちょっとごめん
Stick
Air
Bam
（女子生徒２）
ねえ―
Hey, is it just me, or did she go
overboard with our math final?
今度の期末 数学の範囲 広くない？
（女子生徒３）
ていうか
英語と同じ ２日目だよね
It's also on the same day as English, which doesn't help.
We should probably start studying for it soon.
（女子生徒４）
そろそろ勉強始めないと
まずいよね
How strange. It's like I just up and vanished into thin air.
何だ　突然 俺の存在が空気に…
Would you mind leaving that on for just a little bit longer?
ちょっとの間
これ付けといてくれる？
You see, Kurama,
鞍馬にね―
I have a favor to ask of you.
お願いがあるんだよ
Chemistry Room
Go stand outside the chemistry room now.
（奈々生）
今から科学室の前に行って
There's a girl coming, so wait for her there.
女の子が来るから待ってて
Seriously?!
（鞍馬）
まじかよ
Not a single person is fawning over my presence?!
このビジュアルのカリスマに
誰も寄ってこないとか
Seriously?
まじかよ…
Kurama!
（あみ）
鞍馬君！
I'm late because the teacher asked me to do something.
先生に頼まれものされちゃって
遅れちゃった
あれ？
Huh?
Looking
Seriously?
（鞍馬）
まじかよ
Looking
Here!
Here.
Eep
Oh... The other day...
（あみ）
ああ この前は…
Thank you for helping me.
助けてくれて ありがとう
I never got the chance to thank you, so yeah, thanks for that.
私まだ お礼も言ってなかったから
Who're you again?
君 誰だっけ
（鞍馬）
I got so many feels reading Hanayume yesterday.
（磯辺(いそべ)）
昨日 読んだ 「花ゆめ」
超ときめきよ
Bolting
N-Nobody!
（あみ）
何でもないよ…
Bolting
Splat
Owie...
（あみ）
あ… 痛…
Dude, did you see that? Nekota's panties!
（磯辺）
おい 見たかよ 猫田(ねこた)のパンツ
I-Isobe!
い… 磯辺君
You wear strawberry panties just like a little kid!
いちごのパンツだ
ガキみたいな でっかいいちご！
（御手洗）ハハハ…
（あみ）嫌～！
No!
（磯辺）
いちごパンツ
お前のあだ名は―
Strawberry Panties!
Starting today, your nickname is Strawberry Panties!
今日から
いちごパンツだよ！
Stop it!
（御手洗）アハハ…
（あみ）やめて～
Shut up.
（鞍馬）
うるさい
So you two finally saw a girl's underwear. Big deal.
女の下着見たくらいで
騒ぐな ガキ
You brats.
Kurama.
（御手洗）
鞍馬君
I didn't know you were there.
（磯辺）
いたんだ
We're sorry!
（磯辺･御手洗）
ごめんなさい！
Nekota, right?
（鞍馬）
猫田さんね
Y-Yes...
（あみ）
はい…
And what's your first name?
猫田 何ちゃん？
（あみ）
あみ…
Ami...
Second Sight
Thank goodness.
よかった
Second Sight
It looks like she managed to thank him.
猫田さん 何とかお礼言えたみたい
My divine powers worked pretty well, didn't they?
私の通力もなかなかやるでしょ
Would this count as having made a match?
これって
縁を結んだことになるのかな
（巴衛）
ばか
Idiot.
You thoughtlessly take on random favors without any regard to the consequences.
すぐ安請け合いをするのは
お前の悪いところだな
Why even bother getting that naive girl's hopes up?
あんな 吹けば飛ぶような娘を
あおってどうする
Kurama is a spirit.
鞍馬は 妖怪だ
If that girl finds out the object of her affection isn't even human,
妖怪と縁を結ばれたと
あの娘が知れば―
I doubt she would thank you.
お前に感謝などすまいよ
How do you know?
そんなことないと思うけど
Tomoe's always so negative when it comes to this stuff.
（奈々生）
こういうことになると
巴衛は すぐ否定的になるのよね
Could it be...
もしかして―
that he was cruelly rejected by someone in the past?!
昔 誰かに
こっぴどく振られたとか？
Thwack
Just study!
（巴衛）
いいから 勉強しろ
Tomoe may be unhappy about it, but I made someone's day a little brighter.
（奈々生）
巴衛は浮かない顔だけど
人の役に立てたんだから―
よかったよね きっと
Is that really such a terrible thing to do?
What is it?
（巴衛）何だ
（奈々生）えっ？
What? Nothing.
いや 人も妖怪も仲良くするのは
いいことだと思うっていうか
Teehee
I just think it'd be better for both humans and spirits to get along with each other.
Is there a need for us to get along?
仲良くする必要があるのか？
I think there are humans who'd like to be friends with you too.
巴衛と仲良くしたい人間も
いると思うよ
You should try getting to know some humans.
巴衛も 人と接してみればいいのに
If I...
（巴衛）俺は…
（奈々生）うん？
can protect you, that is all I care about.
お前が守れていれば それでいいよ
Come on. You shouldn't say things like that so casually.
（奈々生）
もう…
そんなことサラッと言わないでよ
（女子生徒）
桃園先輩ですか？
Are you Momozono?
（女子生徒）
ちょっと 話があるんですけど
We'd like to have a word with you.
Me?
私？
（ユミ）
１年の桜田(さくらだ)ユミです
I'm Sakurada Yumi, a first-year.
I like Tomoe, but I've never even talked to him.
（ユミ）
私 巴衛先輩のことが好きで―
でも
一度もお話したことがなくって
Seriously, there are no opportunities ever,
and you two are, like, literally always together.
だって 隙がないっていうか―
いっつも 桃園先輩が
隣にいるっていうか
Basically, I wanted to know if you two are together.
ぶっちゃけ ２人が
つきあってるのか知りたくって
So what is it?
それで どうなんですか
What?
W-We're not together or anything like that.
わ… 私たちは 別に―
つきあってるとか
そんなんじゃないし
Are you for real?! Be honest with me!
本当に？　本当の本当に？
Y-Yeah.
よかった！
I'm so glad!
じゃあ お願い聞いてもらえますか
Then can I ask you for a favor?
You always go home with Tomoe, right?
いっつも
巴衛先輩と一緒に帰ってますよね
Please let me walk home with him today!
今日の帰りは 私に譲ってください
いいよ
Sure.
Thank you so very much!
（ユミ）
ありがとうございます
（奈々生）
大したことじゃない
It's no big deal.
通力なんか使わない
It won't require my divine powers.
I just have to make up an excuse and go home without him.
巴衛に ひと言 断って
先に帰っちゃえばいいだけだもの
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
Bam
Thanks for taking the trash out.
I'll be going on ahead home.
Nanami
（ユミ）
あの 巴衛先輩
Um, Tomoe?
Are you going home alone today?
（ユミ）
今日は お一人で帰られるんですか
よかったら私の…
If you don't mind, would you—
No.
（巴衛）
いや
I am not alone.
一人じゃない
（奈々生）
“オランダ独立宣言 1581年”
Dutch Declaration of Independence, 1581.
World History
Edict of Nantes, 1598.
“ナントの勅令 1598年”
I wonder if Tomoe ended up walking home with that girl.
巴衛 あの子と帰ったかな
You should try getting to know some humans.
人と接してみればいいのに
I wish...
あんなこと…
I'd never said that.
言わなければよかった
Please let me!
（ユミ）
私に譲ってください
（奈々生）
ばかだな
I'm so stupid.
勝手に安請け合いして
勝手に後悔してる
I accepted her request on the spot, and now here I am, regretting it.
This sucks.
最悪だよ
If I knew it was going to bother me this much, I wouldn't've said yes to her.
こんなに モヤモヤするなら
いいよなんて言わなきゃよかった
I like Tomoe.
（ユミ）
私 巴衛先輩が好きで…
Me too.
（奈々生）
私も…
Me too?
私も？
私も…
Me too.
どういう了見だ これは
What is the meaning of this?!
So you wanted me to become friendly with a human girl?
俺に 人間の娘と
仲良くさせたかったわけか
You heard that—
Of course I heard.
（巴衛）
聞いていた
Do you honestly think matching a
human with a spirit is considerate?
仲を取り持とうと
気を利かせたつもりか
You really are a simpleton.
めでたいやつだな
余計な気を遣って
勝手に立ち回るな
Do not set things in motion out of
the so-called kindness of your heart.
俺にとって お前以上に
優先すべきことなどない
In my eyes, there is nothing in this world that takes greater priority over you.
自覚しろ
Get used to it.
With those words, I knew.
（奈々生）
そのひと言で分かってしまった
心揺さぶられる自分に
気付いてしまった
I knew exactly how he made me feel.
I had fallen so hard for him without even realizing it.
知らないうちに―
こんなにも
好きになってしまっている
right up
Next part coming
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Next
part
starting
Well?
で… こんな所に呼び出して
何の用だ　天狗(てんぐ)
What is so important that you asked me to meet you in this foul place, crow?
I overheard your conversation on the roof the other day.
先日 屋上でのお前たちの会話が
耳に入ってきたんでね
Being wise to the ways of the world, I thought I'd give the foolish fox a word of warning.
世慣れした俺が 無知なきつねに
ひと言 忠告してやろうと思ってさ
The conversation on the roof?
（巴衛）
屋上での会話？
俺にとって 奈々生以上に
大事なやつなんていないよ
"There's no one more important to me than you, Nanami.
Get used to it!"
自覚しろ
I believe it went something like that.
とか何とか言ったやつだ
I never said anything of the—
そんなこと言ってない
Good grief.
You're more hopeless than I thought.
うかつな きつねだな
Nanami is at that age where human girls start dating and looking for a mate.
奈々生の年頃を思春期と言って―
普通の娘なら
つがいを求め始める時期だ
You don't want to be the object of a human's affections, right?
人間に ほれられるのは
不本意なんだろう
Be sure to start practicing a little more discretion when you handle her.
もう少し 取り扱いに注意すべきだ
When you consider that she's also your lady and mistress, you've got yourself a serious situation.
おまけに 相手が
自分のあるじときては―
事は重大だよな
Are implying that Nanami is being seduced?
（巴衛）
俺の振る舞いが 奈々生を惑わすと
Being a familiar sounds pretty rough.
神使も大変だよな
Looking after a human—a young girl, at that.
人間の…
しかも 娘の世話なんて
It'd be so much if you made me the land god—
だから 手っとり早く
俺を土地神にしておけば…
（巴衛）
ばかばかしい
This is absurd.
この世で 現在
俺に命令できる 唯一の存在が―
There is only one being in this world who holds the powers to give me orders,
and you would dare say she is like any other schoolgirl that loses her head over petty emotions?
恋だ何だと うつつを抜かす
そこらの娘と同じだと？
Do not take me for a fool, crow.
なめるなよ 天狗
Whatever you say.
It's time.
時間だ
Reference Room
Huh? It won't open.
（女子生徒１）
あれ？　開かないよ
Let me see.
（女子生徒２）どれ…
（女子生徒たち）わっ！
Pardon us.
失礼
Brisk as a breeze
When I become the land god, the first
order I'll give my familiar is to kill himself.
（鞍馬）
俺が神になったら
お前に 死ねって命令してやるよ
（巴衛）
よかったな 夢がでかくてな
You've certainly set some lofty goals for yourself.
What?!
I'm so glad finals are over.
やっと 期末終わったよ
That was rough.
しんどかった
Hey, where did Tomoe go?
（あみ）
あれ？　巴衛君 どこに行ったの？
He mentioned something about picking up stuff with Kurama.
何か 鞍馬と 購買部行くって
出てったけど
I see.
（あみ）
そっか
In that case, why don't we celebrate the end of finals?
Do either of you wanna grab a bite to eat somewhere?
せっかく 試験終わったからさ
みんなで 何か食べて帰らない？
There's a donut shop I highly recommend.
お勧めの ドーナツ屋さんがあるの
I'll pass. I've got a date with my boyfriend.
（ケイ）
私 パス
彼氏とデートだから
What?!
えーっ！
ケイちゃん つきあい悪い
You're being a bad friend, Kei!
Guys come first in my book.
（ケイ）
私は 男を取るよ
A boyfriend, huh?
彼氏か
That must be nice.
いいな
Aren't you going out with Tomoe?
桃園さんって 巴衛君と
つきあってんじゃないの
What?
You're always together, so it made sense to me.
いつも一緒にいるから
てっきり
We do spend time together, but it's not like that.
一緒にはいるけど
それだけっていうか
Our problem is that we're too close to begin with.
なまじ 近くにいると 今更…
He did tell me I mean a lot to him,
大事だとは言ってくれたけど
好きだとかは言われてないし―
but he didn't mean it like that.
We live together, but it's not like
we've ever been on a date or anything.
一緒に住んでるけど
２人で遊びに行ったこととかないし
Is she bragging?
のろけ？
N-No!
ち… 違う
If you two aren't as close as you wanna be, why not try switching things up on him now and then?
関係が進展しないってんなら
いつもと違うこととかしてみたら？
How would I do that?
違うことって…
You've never been on a date, right?
（ケイ）
デートしたことないんでしょう
Then try going out on an actual date.
だったら デートしてみるとか
Try going somewhere you haven't been before and act super cute.
行ったことない所に行ってみて
うんとかわいく振る舞うの
A-Act cute?
（奈々生）
か… かわいく
Yes
No
Send?
Yes
No
Sending
When guys think a girl is cute, they'll naturally want more.
かわいいって思うとね
自然と男は触ってくるよ
Oh, could it be...
あっ もしかして…
Wide-Eyed
that you like Tomoe, Momozono?!
桃園さんって
巴衛君のこと好きなの？
What?
Welcome to five minutes ago, Ami.
（ケイ）
あみ あんた 会話ずれてるね
A place he's never been before?
（奈々生）
いつもと違うこと？
Nanami.
（巴衛）
奈々生
Time to go home.
帰るぞ
Right.
Tomoe is always in a hurry to get home.
（奈々生）
巴衛は いつも家路を急ぐ
I know he's worried about taking care of the shrine.
社の仕事を放ったままだと言って
But...
だけど…
Hey, Tomoe.
（奈々生）ねえ 巴衛
（巴衛）うん？
Since school got out early today, let's not rush back home so fast.
まだ 昼過ぎだし
ちょっと どこか寄ってかない？
Right now's the perfect time for an adventure.
今日は 違うことしてみよう
We're here! The aquarium!
来た～！　水族館
I haven't been here since elementary school!
小学校の遠足以来だ
Friends
with Dolphins!
Schedule
It says this aquarium has a dolphin splash show!
この水族館 イルカの
スプラッシュショーがあるんだって
Let's go!
行こう！
Hey, what are you trying to pull?!
おい 何なんだ 急に
Exams are over, so it's time for us to relax!
（奈々生）
テスト終わったから 息抜きだよ
We've already here, so we might as well enjoy it!
せっかく来たんだから
遊んで帰ろう　ねっ
Wow, that one's gigantic!
わあ すごい迫力
Marine fish sure are big.
やっぱり 海の魚は大きいな
Don't you think so, Tomoe?
ねえ 巴衛
Wait...
って どこ行ってんのよ！
Where are you going?!
Grab
This is the route, right?
こっちが順路だろう
Look at the fish!
魚見ろ！　魚！
Fish!
It's not working.
駄目だ
He's looked miserable the entire time.
全然 楽しそうじゃないかも
つきあわせてる雰囲気 むんむん
He's oozing resentment at being forced to tag along.
I have to do something.
何とかしなきゃ
Oh, I wonder what that crowd's about!
あっ 何だろう あの人だかり
Let's check it out, Tomoe. It looks like a sea lion's going to do a skit.
見てみようよ 巴衛
アシカが コントやるみたいだよ
A lot of friends have gathered here to see you today.
（インストラクター）
今日は たくさんのお友達が
集まってくれましたよ
I can't see because of all the people.
（奈々生）
人が多くて 見えない
（インストラクター）
うまい！
Mag-neigh-ficent!
Were you able to see?
（巴衛）
見えたか
Y-Yes.
（奈々生）
は… はい
Good.
（巴衛）
よし
Time to go.
行くぞ
遅い
You are slow.
When guys think a girl is cute,
（ケイ）
かわいいって思うとね
自然と 男は触ってくるよ
they'll naturally want more.
Really?
（奈々生）
本当に…
Really?
本当に？
よしよし
魚も たくさん見られたし―
All right then.
You were able to see lots of fish, so you must be quite satisfied.
奈々生も さぞかし
満足したことだろう
What a happy ending to this grand adventure!
ああ めでたしめでたし
Grab
Now let's go!
さあ 帰るぞ！
Grab
W-Wait!
（奈々生）
ま… 待って
We've gotta make the most of this trip.
せっかく来たんだから
あっ ほら あれ
Look there. Let's go enjoy the night view first.
夜景見ていこうよ
もうちょっと　もうちょっとだけ
A little more...
Just a little more!
Just a little while longer!
あと 少しだけ
Hurry up, will ya?!
巴衛 早く
Wow!
What an incredible view!
すごい 絶景
カメラ持ってくればよかった
I should've brought my camera.
Do you think we can see our place from here?
うち ここから見えるかな
What do you think?
ねえ 巴衛
Stare
What's wrong?
何？
You have been acting strange today.
お前 今日は変だな
You seem more excited and cheerful than usual.
妙に明るく振る舞って
落ち着きがない
Surely the fish and the night view didn't cause this transformation.
そんなに 魚と夜景が
見たかったわけでもあるまい
Th-That's not—
そ… そんなこと…
There is one thing I want to ask you...
（巴衛）
一つ 聞いておきたいことが
あるのだが
You have not fallen for me, right?
お前 俺に懸想してないだろうな
It was something the crow said.
天狗が言っていたのだが―
Human girls your age start becoming interested in finding love. He implied you are no exception.
思春期の娘は 男に色めきやすく
お前も例外でないと
He warned me that I must not speak in a
manner to make you fall in love with me.
俺との主従関係を 色恋沙汰に
すげ替える危険があると
Well, the crow loves his jokes. Forget I mentioned it.
まあ 天狗のざれ言だな
忘れろ
What if I said it was true?
（奈々生）
そうだって言ったら？
If I did like you...
（奈々生）
私が 巴衛のこと―
What would you say if he was right?
好きって言ったらどうするのよ
（巴衛）
気… 気の迷いだ
Y-You are deluding yourself.
N-No, I'm not!
ち… 違うよ
What if what I'm really feeling is...
私 本当に 巴衛が好…
lo...
I...
（巴衛）
俺は―
will never allow myself to love a human woman.
人間の女など 好きにならないよ
うわーっ！　落ちる 落ちる！
We're going to fall! We're going to fall!
Let us hope the cool night breeze can bring you to your senses.
（巴衛）
うんと夜風に当たって
頭を冷やすといい
I will wait until you come to your senses.
目が覚めるまで 待っててやろう
Admit that you are delusional, and I will let you down.
気の迷いだったと認めれば
下ろしてやる
I won't do it!
言わない！
Because I really do have feelings for you!
私は 巴衛のこと好きなんだもん！
You told me yourself that I was important to you!
私のこと 大事だって言ったくせに
Never mind that!
言ったが…
So you really never felt the same way about me?
巴衛は
私のこと 好きじゃなかった？
And you never even once found me attractive? Not even for a single moment?
私のこと かわいいって 一度も
思ってくれたことなかったの？
Nanami!
奈々生！
I've been rejected.
（奈々生）
フラれた 私…
Getting my hopes up like that...
一人で浮かれて ばかみたいだった
How was I so stupid?
I can't look Tomoe in the face anymore.
巴衛の顔 もう 見られない
見られないよ
I just can't!
Nanami!
（巴衛）
奈々生！
こっちだ 手を伸ばせ！
Over here! Give me your hand!
Tomoe...
（奈々生）
巴衛？
No! Don't help me!
やだ 助けないで
Zoom
What did you say to me?
何言って…
Don't touch me!
触んないで！
The Sacred Word...
（巴衛）
言霊が
You idiot! Do you want to die?!
このばか　死にたいのか！
If you never even liked me,
you can just stay away from me!
（奈々生）
私のこと好きじゃないくせに
触んないで！
（巴衛）
奈々生… 奈々生
Nanami... Nanami!
Please!
頼む！
I promise you that I will never touch you again,
もう二度と
お前に触れないと約束するから―
but for now, you have to let me save you!
今だけは助けさせてくれ！
He's so kind and strong and warm.
（奈々生）
こんなに優しくて 強くて
温かいのに…
How could I ever give up on him?
諦めろなんて―
It isn't fair.
ずるい
ah ah ah ah
Nanami?
奈々生
ah ah ah ah
It's no use.
（奈々生）
止められないよ
I know that my love for him will just keep growing.
きっと もっと好きになってく
kamisama onegai da
Please, God
boku no
I...
ano hito ni aitai no sa
I want to meet her
ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah
kamisama tsurain da
God, I'm in pain
kyou mo mata nou ni
Because, she...
konakatta
didn't come today either.
onegai ga aru no kamisama
I have a request, God
boku wo tasukete
Please, save me
ah ah ah ah
kamisama mou osoi
God, it's too late for me
ano ko wa...
Because she's...
Ah! Nanami's declaration of love ends in heartbreak.
Preview
（講釈師）
ああ 奈々生 勇気の告白も
巴衛の前で ハートブレイク
Touku sora ni
gone off into the distant sky
What better place to get over a rejection than at the beach?
傷心引きずってやって来たのは
白い砂浜
Kieta no sa
and disappeared
But a dark shadow rises from the sea.
しかし 海から黒い影
Yeah, yeah, yeah
He says he has business with Tomoe. Who in the world is this guy?!
巴衛に用があるって
こいつ 一体 何者？
Sayonara baby
Farewell, baby
次回「神様、海へいく」
Next time, "The God Goes To The Beach."
The God Goes To The Beach
Summer! Bikinis! Swim trunks!
夏だ！　ビキニだ！　海パンだ
Goodbye